♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
Hey, everybody.
Wow, that's a tough break.
You've got to be kidding!
Unfortunately, I'm not.
Hey, uh, what's going on here?
I wish I could do something, Yumi.
That's really nice of you, Aelita.
But…
would somebody tell me what's going on?
Look, we'll talk about it after class, okay?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Don’t mind me!
Keep making like I don’t exist. Okay?
Say that again.
Yumi's father lost his job.
They're thinking of going back to Japan so he can find work.
You've got to be kidding!
It's not for sure yet, so don't panic.
What?
Yumi's leaving, we may never see her again,
and I shouldn't panic?
You know what?
There is an easy solution.
Oh yeah? What?
Well uh, you see, if you marry Yumi,
then she can get a greencard!
Very funny.
I’m just trying to lighten things up.
Por favor, senor Cadja
Si Ulrich?
Can I please go to the infirmary?
I’m not feeling too well.
In Moby Dick,
Melville uses the literary technique
of a character in the novel speaking-
Excuse me ma’am?
Yes, Yumi?
Could I please go to the infirmary?
Why can’t you stay at the school as a boarder?
And you could go to Japan during summer vacation.
Are you kidding?
My parents would never go for that.
And what’s more, they need me.
Isn’t it supposed to be the
other way around?
What if-?
Ulrich, it’s nice of you
to try find a solution,
but nothing has been settled.
There might not be anything
to worry about.
I know!
Why don’t we write to a
congressmen and ask for help?
Sure, why not the
president while you’re at it!
Are you ready for dinner?
You go on, I’ll see you there.
Dear Mr. President.
I’m writing to you about a
young girl named Yumi.
Yumi is an amazing person.
She’s originally from Japan,
but she really likes her country.
Uhh, what a load of garbage.
Dear Mr. President...
Will you be quiet?
Can’t you see I’m trying to concentrate?
...remember folks this weeks super jackpot
is 30 million big ones!
And now that big bonus number, 14.
Two times lucky seven, 14.
Anyway…
...remember folks this weeks super jackpot
is 30 million big ones!
No, I couldn’t do that…
It wouldn’t be right.
Did you go back to
see the temp agencies?
I haven’t had time.
Too bad, they might’ve
had something for you.
I mean, to tide us over
until we return to Kyoto.
There is nothing
out there for me,
There are too many people in my field.
You know that very well.
Anyway, if you don’t look, you certainly won’t find anything.
Oh, will you stop it now? What about you?
Did you go to the temp agencies today?
Hmm?
(BARKS)
He’s not in our room. I don’t know where he is.
I get the feeling that Ulrich is taking
this situation even harder than we are.
You can say that again.
For Ulrich, losing Yumi is…
Well, imagine how you’d
feel if Jeremie had to leave.
Why do you say that?
‘Cause I love making you blush.
Wait, what just happened?
Why did we return to the past?
Could XANA have taken control of the back-in-time function?
He’s done it before.
No way. I made a special program
so he couldn’t.
The superscan doesn’t show any active towers.
This is really weird.
I’ll go to the factory after class and check it out.
Here you go.
Uh, you do know that you’re not
really old enough to play, young man?
Oh, it’s for my mom.
She asked me to buy it for her.
Ah, well in that case...
Ulrich, we’re gonna check out things
at the factory after class.
About the jump back in time.
You coming?
No, I, uh… I have to, uh, study for chemistry.
Hey, mind if I study with you?
I don’t get Mendeleev’s Periodic Table at all.
I’d rather study by myself.
Huh?
Well, I know you’re gonna think this is ridiculous.
But I heard you had some problems with work and everything.
And I thought, well…
I bought you a lotto ticket!
You never know, maybe you’ll be lucky.
Then you could stay here, with Yumi.
(LAUGHS)
I’m sorry, son, but you have to admit that it is very funny.
Do you know the odds of winning the lotto?
Heh, at least you made me laugh.
That’s something I need right now.
Anyway, it was very nice of you, Ulrich,
we’re really touched.
Don’t forget to listen for the numbers!
Oh, and please don’t tell Yumi
that I gave it to you! She might take it the wrong way.
That Ulrich is such a sweetheart.
Yes, only he doesn’t realize that we have
one chance in fourteen million of ever winning.
Now, once again, today’s lotto results!
The winning numbers for today’s
super jackpot drawing are...
6, 22, 10, 47, 13, 37
and the bonus number is… 14!
I can’t believe it…
Hey there, what’s going on?
This is the winning ticket… the jackpot!
What’s a jackpot?
It’s incredible!
You played the lotto? But I thought you hated gambling.
Actually, it was your friend Ulrich who played,
and he gave us the ticket.
He didn’t want you to know.
I don’t get it. XANA had nothing to do with it.
It’s as if someone had
set off the return to the past from here.
Except that I’m the only one that knows how to do it.
Unless… someone read your manual.
What makes you say that?
Hi.
Hi, Ulrich. You know, I’m really impressed
with your computer skills.
Who, me? You are?
Well, you did enter the code for returning to the past into the computer
without making a single mistake, well done.
What are you talking about?
Don’t waste your breath. We know it was you who set off the return to the past.
You broke rule number one, Ulrich, I can’t believe it.
I only did it for Yumi, so you could stay.
I didn’t ask for your help.
Do you realize what you’ve done, Ulrich?
You know that going back
in time makes XANA stronger!
Why didn’t you talk to us first, huh?
Why did you have to go sneaking around?
I’m sorry…
It’s too late for sorry. You betrayed our trust.
Here. You can take back your dumb ticket.
My parents think you should keep the money.
As of now, and until you hear otherwise,
you’re out of the group, Ulrich.
I hope this will all work out.
Hey, what’s up, Ulrich?
You don’t look too good.
You’re right. And when I see you, it gets even worse.
That’ll teach me to be nice to people.
Sissi, wait.
I apologize.
I’m just a little edgy.
I really don’t understand what she sees in him.
You said it. He sure is no match for my looks or my brains.
Hmph. You think you’re handsome, huh?
No more than you think you’re smart.
I dare you to say that again!
Africa is the continent that suffers most
from problems related to a shortage of water
and rural areas of Africa
are affected to an even greater extent.
Less than half of all rural zones
have any access to--
Wow, when I think how much
we complain all the time…
XANA has launched an attack.
What?
We have less than a minute left of class. We’ll go to the factory as soon as the bell rings.
Without Ulrich?
Without Ulrich.
See you next week, then.
Hey, Nicolas!
And don’t forget your project reports
on your own ideas for helping African communities.
Transfer Aelita.
Transfer Yumi.
Transfer Odd.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Aelita.
Scanner Yumi.
Virtualization!
Here come your vehicles.
Madame, would you do me the honor
of climbing aboard my humble… board?
(GIGGLES)
The activated tower is located two plateaus north.
Okay, let’s go.
Yeah!
No monsters on the horizon for the time being.
It’s not monsters I’m worried about.
It’s XANA attack on Earth.
We still don’t know what he’s got in store for us this time.
Yeah, well, I’d rather we deactivated
the tower before we find out.
Aah!
At your orders, XANA.
Look! Over there, a Krab!
Are my eyes playing tricks on me,
or are there at least twenty of them?
Yumi, there are no mirages on Lyoko.
That’s what I was afraid of.
By the way, thanks for warning us, Jeremie!
Jeremie?
Now your wounds will become fatal!
(LAUGHS)
Jeremie, was that you?
Answer me, will you?
That isn’t Jeremie, I’d recognize that laugh anywhere.
It’s Nicolas.
Nicolas? Are you sure?
Nobody else has a laugh that dumb.
No one in the whole universe!
Watch out, the Krabs!
We better get out of here, fast!
Yumi!
Yumi, are you okay?
I don’t understand, why does it hurt so much? Shouldn’t I just lose some life points?
Something’s wrong at the factory.
Odd, the Krabs.
We’re gonna have to take cover.
You’re even more handsome when you train.
Sissi, I think I’d rather be alone.
Are you crazy?
That’s the last thing you need when you’re feeling down.
It’s just the opposite, you need your friends to be there.
Uh-uh. I don’t have friends anymore.
What about me?
What does that make me, then?
Sissi, there you are!
I’ve been looking all over for you!
Yeah? Well, pretend I’m not here
and keep on looking.
Why don’t you go out and play
with your friend Nicolas?
I would, but I can’t find Nicolas, either.
He ran off like a madman after class
to follow Jeremie, Odd, and the new girl.
He was really spaced out.
His voice sounded weird
and there was something strange about his eyes.
XANA.
Why are you telling me all this?
I don’t care. Can’t you see I’m with Ulrich?
Well, not anymore, you’re not.
Huh?
I’ll go and check it out.
We’d better move. Otherwise--
Wow, that really does hurt.
My turn.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
It won’t take them long to find a way around.
Jeremie?
Maybe I know what you’re looking for!
Wow, since when have you become an athlete?
I don’t believe it.
Come on, Spiderman.
Hold on, I’m not out yet.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Jeremie, wake up, will you?
You gotta get up!
Hey… hi, Ulrich, how are you?
Jeremie, pull yourself together,
I need your help.
...because I’m not feeling so great.
Odd, Yumi, Aelita, can you hear me?
Answer me, will ya?
Ulrich, is that you?
Oh great, you’re alive.
Yeah, but not in great shape.
What about Jeremie?
He’s also in pretty bad shape.
I don’t get it, there’s nothing on the screens.
That must be why the fire
from XANA’s monsters hurt us for real!
What was that noise?
It’s just what I was afraid of.
The Krabs have broken through the sand wall!
I’m really sorry about this, Jeremie,
but it’s for a good cause.
Ouch! What--
what’s going on?
Okay, this is no time to drag your feet.
Nicolas has deactivated the scanner.
I should be able to fix it pretty fast.
Jeremie, I, uh, wanted to tell you--
Later! Head for the scanner and get ready!
Come on!
Yumi, no!
Yes!
Yeah, we’re invincible again!
Hold on, I’m sending you Ulrich.
Jeremie!
Transfer, Ulrich.
Scanner, Ulrich.
Laser arrow!
Virtualization!
Hi, guys.
Didn’t miss me too much, did you?
Just a little, yeah.
Yeah, but those guys aren't gonna
keep missing us if we stick around.
Your vehicles are on the way.
They could come in handy.
Okay, great. Now all we have to do
is cross that line of monsters.
You and Yumi may as well go over the top.
And what about you?
I’ll do what I do best.
Chef’s surprise.
Come on, Aelita.
We haven’t much time.
Woah!
He’s really lost it this time.
No more than you have.
Come on, let’s go.
Yaaah!
They’re never gonna make it!
Oh no!
Another row of those guys!
Stop moving around so much!
How do you expect me to help you?
Cut me some slack, okay?
I’m just trying to avoid getting hit.
Now!
Jeremie, I think we’ve done it.
Ulrich, you’re the greatest!
Hey, what about me?
Don’t I get any credit?
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
No!
Tower deactivated.
You say this is how he was when you found him?
Yeah, in the middle of the campus.
Hm.
That’s very strange, he must have fainted.
Nothing serious, in any case.
I know you did it for me, Ulrich.
But I should’ve asked you first.
Right.
I’m sorry.
So, are you back in the group?
Hmm, looks like it.
Hey, what are you gonna do
with that lotto ticket?
I thought about it, and I decided to give it
to an association that builds wells in Africa.
Really?
Oh, that’s a great idea!
(PHONE RINGS)
Yes?
Yeah, Mom, I’m listening.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Alright, see you tonight.
My father’s found work with Takahashi.
Takahashi? You mean, in Japan?
No, silly, right here!
Oh…
(CHEERING)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED
BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS!